[♪ theme music playing]
WOULD YOU MARRY ME?
ALL CHARACTERS, PLACES,
ORGANIZATIONS, ETC. ARE FICTIONAL
CHILD ACTORS WERE FILMED
WITH GUARDIANS PRESENT
ANIMALS WERE FILMED
UNDER EXPERT SUPERVISION AND WELFARE RULES
[♪ gentle pop music playing]
YOUNGSOOK'S RESTAURANT
CEO YOO MERI
[line ringing]
[phone vibrating]
Hey, did you find it?
[Wooju] It's me.
How have you been?
[♪ gripping dramatic music playing]
I'm back.
I'm in Seoul.
-As soon as I landed...
-[line disconnects]
Hello? Hel...
[line connects]
[automated voice] The call can't
be connected. Transferring to voicemail.
You will be charged after the tone.
[line disconnects]
Sure.
You must have some pride in yourself.
Play hard to get once.
WOOJU
That scared me.
He told me never to call him.
[gasps]
Why did he call me?
Does he know something?
TEAM LEADER KIM WOOJU
[phone vibrating]
Hello?
I found it.
It was in the door gap.
Oh, that's a relief.
No, I'll come and get it.
I have a meeting there anyway.
Oh, and...
Should I tell him that Wooju called?
What is it? Do you have something to say?
No, I'll see you tomorrow.
[line disconnects]
I shouldn't bother him for no reason.
I feel bad about everything already.
[exhales deeply]
Are you still up?
Yes, I couldn't sleep.
Were you out somewhere?
-Oh, at the garage.
-I see.
How is work?
You don't work for fun. You just work.
What?
[both chuckle]
I'm a total workaholic these days.
I have no work-life balance,
and I'm completely committed.
You should relax
now that Uncle and I are around.
Go on trips and dates.
Enjoy life a bit.
Why would I go on dates?
[chuckles softly] I'd abandon my husband
if I had one.
Look at all the old women who are happy.
They're all widows.
Only those with their husbands alive
look glum and distraught.
By the way, if you have anybody,
bring her to see me.
Someone worthy of marrying
the head of Myungsoondang.
Marrying well is one of your duties.
-Okay.
-Take what I say seriously.
Everyone's watching you.
[♪ soft, gentle music playing]
Don't forget
you must live for your dad, too.
Only then will your grandpa
get over his anger in the afterlife.
Do you know what I mean?
I do. I'll do my best.
Let's go inside.
Sure.
[door lock beeps open]
[♪ gripping whimsical music playing]
-[Sanghyeon] You're off to work early.
-[Meri exclaims]
Good morning.
Did your husband leave already?
His car isn't in the parking lot.
[acknowledges]
He worked late last night.
He must be incredibly busy these days.
[hums thoughtfully]
Do you need a ride to the bus stop?
No, it's fine.
I love to contemplate on my way to work.
[acknowledges]
Why don't we have
breakfast together one day?
You know the cafeteria here
serves breakfast, don't you?
Yes, that would be nice.
Okay, then.
[Meri] Sure.
Drive on.
[♪ upbeat pop music playing]
[chuckles softly]
[sighs]
I should leave at the crack of dawn now.
WOULD YOU MARRY ME?
EPISODE 5
[chuckles] Welcome, Mr. Baek.
Pleasure to meet you.
I'm Baek Sanghyeon of Beauté.
Yes, thank you for making the trip over.
This is our CFO.
I'm Jang Hangu.
I heard a lot about you from Mr. Lee.
Oh, I see.
-Let's sit down.
-Sure.
Director Jang,
you're acquainted with Mr. Lee?
Yes, we went to business school together.
We play golf, too, sometimes.
-[acknowledges]
-He meant to join us today,
but he is currently hospitalized,
so I'm here on my own.
Oh, my. Why is he in the hospital?
It's nothing serious.
He should watch his health.
Your health is your biggest asset.
I told him to get some well-earned rest.
He asked me to send
some of our croquettes with Mr. Baek.
-[hesitates]
-[all chuckling]
We should pack him the best-tasting ones.
[chuckles] Yes, I'll do that.
-Have some tea.
-Yes, thanks.
[Kim Wooju] A VVIP package?
Yes, Beauté Department Store will gift
our hangwa set to their VVIP customers
to celebrate their anniversary.
-Beauté Department Store?
-Yes.
[phone vibrates]
[Meri] I'd like to come
and get the wallet.
Are you free?
[Kim Wooju] Yes,
call me when you get here.
[telephone ringing]
Hello, Kim Wooju speaking.
[line disconnects]
I told Mr. Kim to come over.
You might as well meet the Head
of Marketing you'll be working with.
Sure, that's fine with me.
Good morning. Go on inside.
I heard someone
from the Beauté Department Store was here.
Yes, Managing Director Baek Sanghyeon.
[stutters] Who? Baek Sanghyeon?
Yes.
[♪ gripping dramatic music playing]
No, wait.
[hesitates]
I need to take an urgent bathroom break.
-Pardon?
-[grunts, farts]
[groans]
Oh, I see.
-Go ahead.
-Thanks. [groaning]
CEO
KO PHILNYUN
[farts, grunts]
Should I leave work early?
[sighs] No, it's too random.
Oh, a business meeting elsewhere.
Don't I have one of those?
JULY
SECRETARY'S OFFICE
[gasps]
[phone vibrating]
Yes, hello?
Oh, well, you see,
I'm having some bathroom issues.
I can't come right away.
Right, could you talk to Mr. Jang for me?
Thank you.
[line disconnects]
[sighs deeply]
Everyone will call me a pooper now.
[♪ whimsical sting]
[Hangu] Mr. Kim?
[♪ dramatic guitar music playing]
Mr. Jang.
I'm glad you two get to meet.
This is Kim Wooju, our Head of Marketing.
This is Beauté Department Store's
Managing Director Baek.
[mumbles]
Hello.
It's nice to meet you.
Nice to meet you, too.
I'm Baek Sanghyeon.
[chuckles]
[Hangu] This is great. [chuckles softly]
-I'll see you again soon.
-Drive back safely.
-See him off.
-Sure thing.
[elevator button beeps]
So, this is where you work.
Well, yes.
I pretended not to know you
in case you felt uncomfortable.
Separating work from life
is very important
when dealing with business partners.
Letting mistakes slide
because you're acquaintances?
I don't care much for personal connections
forged in school or social circles.
Of course. Not in this day and age.
I agree with you completely.
[chuckles softly]
Thank you for understanding.
[acknowledges]
Since we're on the topic,
-could I ask for a favor?
-I know.
You want me to keep your secret, right?
[Sanghyeon] The winners used false names?
The couple was terrified
that the creditors would come after them.
They begged me to keep it a secret.
They insisted we use false names
in the articles we release.
Yes, that's right.
I'm in debt,
so I won't have much left
even if I were to sell the unit.
[♪ dramatic guitar music playing]
You look pretty good
for someone who worked late last night.
I worked late?
[elevator dings]
[♪ dramatic sting]
Hey, Mr. Ki...
Honey.
Oh, honey.
What are you doing here, Mr. Baek?
[clears throat] He's here for work.
-For work?
-Yes.
Do you work here, too, Ms. Yoo?
-I'm not employed here--
-Her wallet.
-She's here for her wallet.
-Oh, yes.
He took my wallet with him to work.
This is my wallet.
-[chuckles softly]
-[exclaims in realization]
When a married couple lives together,
-their belongings get mixed up.
-[Meri] Yes.
-Hers is mine, and mine's hers.
-Right.
I left in a hurry early this morning
and wasn't paying attention.
-This morning--
-Yesterday morning.
Sweetie, you worked late last night.
You've been so busy
that yesterday and today
-just blur together, right?
-Oh, it was yesterday.
I've been so scatterbrained these days.
He's pretty out of it.
[Kim Wooju chuckles nervously]
I'll go ahead, then.
-Yes, get back safely.
-Goodbye.
[sighs]
[sighs in exasperation]
-Do you think that went okay?
-Yes.
[exhales]
What? You're working
with Managing Director Baek?
I won't deal with him directly,
but we must be as careful as possible.
[sighs nervously]
We met this morning,
and he asked about you.
I said you worked late last night.
I worked late?
You look pretty good
for someone who worked late last night.
[exclaims in realization]
You should've told me about that.
I need time to plan a defense.
I didn't think you'd meet like this.
From now on,
call right away if you see Mr. Baek.
No, call me three times a day,
no exceptions.
At breakfast, lunch, and dinner.
-Three times a day?
-Yes.
We must share our day
to prevent messing up.
[chuckles] Do we have to go that far?
That naive mindset
caused what just happened.
And, well...
Newlyweds call each other
a dozen times a day.
We're not actual newlyweds.
-Aren't you too into this?
-"Too into this?"
[♪ feel-good music playing]
[stutters] Do you think
I'm doing this for me?
I'm not. I just want to prevent risk.
I'm a busy man, you know.
I know you are.
At breakfast, lunch, and dinner.
Oh, and one more time before bed.
Four times a day.
And we'll talk before bed.
-Okay.
-[phone vibrates]
[Songhee] Where are you, Ms. Yoo?
The meeting's about to start.
I'll go upstairs first.
You can come in a bit later.
It would look weird
if we came in together.
Yes, right.
[chuckles softly]
[clears throat]
-[hums in satisfaction]
-[meowing]
The laver is good. Where is it from?
Hey, I seasoned it myself.
With a mix of perilla oil and sesame oil.
I followed a famous cook's recipe
just to feed you.
[both chuckle]
-Did you?
-Yes.
[meowing]
Did you meet Jenny's parents?
Why would I meet them?
Why didn't you pay them a visit
while you were in Hong Kong?
[mouthing] Hurry over here.
-[clears throat]
-[Elizabeth meowing]
Hey!
Introduce her to us quickly
before she changes her mind.
There's an opening on the main road
where the ice cream shop was.
I need to put down a deposit soon.
[cutlery clatters on plate]
Do you want to marry me off
so you can open your own store?
Exactly.
Let's benefit
from my handsome brother for once.
Gosh! Forget it!
[meows]
Hey, where are you going?
You didn't finish your food.
Hey!
They expect so much from me.
What should I tell them?
No, wait.
[♪ jazz music playing over speakers]
You mean
you and the guy in Room 3613
-are getting married?
-Yes.
Our families made a pact
when we were young.
[loudly] Why are you telling me that now?
I thought we...
[mumbles]
You never said you had a fiancé.
You never asked.
[sighs in disbelief]
[chuckles softly]
Baby, are you jealous?
Don't worry.
My fiancé goes abroad a lot for work.
-I'll have time for you when he's gone.
-Jenny.
I gave up everything for you.
How can you do this to me?
-What do you want me to do?
-You must choose!
You can never have two husbands.
It's him or me.
Who do you choose?
Then...
-[buzzer sounds]
-You're out.
Drink your tea. It's nice.
[♪ dramatic sting]
[sighs wearily]
[Wooju] What should I do with Elizabeth?
[Jenny] I'm busy planning my wedding.
Leave her with my relative.
I'll text you the address.
[♪ gentle pop music playing]
[breath trembling]
EVERYTHING I WANT TO DO WITH YOU
-[Wooju] Meri.
-Yes?
Why do you like me?
Because you're good-looking.
[Wooju chuckles]
You're so cute.
To Meri...
I was her one and only.
I'm sorry, Meri.
[die-cut machine clicks rhythmically]
[die-cut machine beeping]
It's for food packaging,
so it should be moisture-proof,
but it won't look or feel fancy
if the paper's too stiff.
What's this? "Pergraphics?"
We imported that from Austria
to test it out.
It's nice and smooth.
-It's nice, isn't it?
-It is.
N Design ordered some boxes
to send out a cosmetics gift set,
and people are loving it.
Do you have any left?
How many do you need?
About 500 in the size
of the beef jerky sets I got last time.
Let me have a look.
[phone vibrating]
PARK GYEONGHWA
Hey, Gyeonghwa. Are you done?
[knock at door]
My goodness. Are you next? Come on in.
-Hello.
-Take a seat.
[Gyeonghwa] Man, these defense seminars
really bored me.
I'd rather die, you know?
Why didn't you just die, then?
How could you say that?
[chuckles softly]
Pyongyang naengmyeon?
-Minus the cucumber.
-Yes.
Auntie.
Yes?
I'm really sorry, ladies.
It's the lunchtime rush.
Can I let someone join you?
[chuckles] You over there.
Come sit over here.
[chuckles]
Hey.
[♪ whimsical sting]
[♪ gripping whimsical music playing]
I'm Meri's friend, Park Gyeonghwa.
Oh, I heard a lot about you.
Her army friend.
When did you tell him about me?
[both chuckle softly]
Talk normally.
-Was that weird?
-Yes.
[mumbles, clears throat]
-[clears throat]
-How do you know of this place?
It's a hidden gem
only a few people know about.
My boss from when I worked in New York
knew this place.
He loved Pyongyang naengmyeon
and often mentioned this place.
-[Gyeonghwa] Eat up.
-Yes, thanks. [chuckles]
[inhales deeply]
[Gyeonghwa slurping]
[continues slurping, stops]
Your smile. It reminds me of him.
His eyes were just as pretty.
-Who...
-My first love.
[Kim Wooju exclaims]
[chuckles] I see.
[♪ enthralling orchestral music playing]
[Kim Wooju slurping]
[Gyeonghwa] His skull...
His head shape was petite and pretty,
just like yours.
It looked so nice when shaved.
[Meri] Darn you. Stop it.
-Her first love became a Buddhist monk.
-[exclaims quizzically]
He shaved his head to move into a temple,
and I cut mine short to join the army.
We shared a farewell drink right here.
With a small plate of boiled pork.
[exclaims in realization]
That must've broken your heart.
Such is life. It can get salty with tears.
Oh, sure.
First love is like an installment
savings plan that's meant to be canceled.
Pretend he's out there doing just fine.
You can say that
about your boy, Occipital.
There's a boy we call Occipital.
Her elementary school first love.
[acknowledges]
Myungsik...
Who's Myungsik?
-The same guy.
-[Gyeonghwa] Oh, really?
Anyway, she gave him her favorite toy,
but he rejected her without a thank-you.
-A toy?
-Yes.
She gave it to him out of pity
because he was shaking after a car crash.
Ever since, she's been giving,
and everyone takes advantage of her.
-You got off on the wrong foot.
-[exclaims]
You talk too much.
Will you eat until tomorrow?
Sorry.
So, that's why...
He's called Occipital
because he had a cute head.
It was very spherical.
The kind that makes you want to touch it.
[♪ dreamy pop music playing]
[♪ ethereal sparkle]
Did you ever see him since then?
Yeosu's pretty small.
You'd have crossed paths once.
He wasn't from there, I guess.
No?
You don't remember him at all?
No.
We met really briefly.
If we were to meet again,
I'd recognize him right away.
He was so good-looking.
He was totally my type.
I bet he grew up to be just as handsome.
[Gyeonghwa] This place doesn't disappoint.
-Thanks for the meal.
-Thanks for paying.
I'll treat you
to kaoliang liquor next time.
I know a place with fine five-spice pork.
Sounds good.
And this is...
-[Kim Wooju] What's this?
-It's a souvenir I got
from today's defense seminar.
It's an aftershave for men.
But I don't have a man to give it to.
[giggles]
[chuckles] Thanks a lot.
[exclaims]
-What's this?
-Oh, that?
It's for you.
-Am I your trash can?
-Take it already.
Don't sit on that one.
[♪ upbeat pop music playing]
[Meri grunts]
[acknowledges, chuckles softly]
-Okay.
-[both chuckle]
The taxi's here. You should get in.
-We'll go somewhere for tea.
-Okay, then.
-Bye, I'll be in touch.
-Okay.
[hesitates]
[Gyeonghwa] What a pity
we must let him go.
Why would you be in touch with him?
-You go too far.
-What's wrong with that?
There's a boy we call Occipital.
Her elementary school first love.
He was so good-looking.
He was totally my type.
I bet he grew up to be just as handsome.
You're fine, as you always were.
-My neck and shoulders still feel stiff.
-[neck cracking]
And my eyes are dry.
I request a brain MRI.
[Jingyeong sighs]
That's because you play games all day.
You have a tech neck and poor eyesight.
My stomach burns, and I have indigestion.
I request a gastroscopy.
[snaps fingers] Under sedation.
[chuckles softly]
-[squelch]
-[screams]
[groans softly]
You're fine.
That was meant to hurt.
Why did you do that, then?
[scoffs]
Doctor.
Your patient says he's in pain.
[sighs]
[♪ whimsical music playing]
[Jingyeong] Gosh, you snack a lot.
Dried fishcake, dried squid, beef jerky.
[scoffs softly]
You eat stuff that's bad for you
late at night.
It would give anyone indigestion.
[Jingyeong gasps]
[chuckles]
And in this sacred hospital room...
you've even been drinking?
I haven't been able to sleep.
That's my sleeping aid.
Do you like wine?
-Confiscate this from now on.
-Yes, Doctor.
You're a terrible patient,
but you're just as bad
for getting him whatever he wants.
You can go home before this weekend.
Doctor.
I request an extended stay.
The patient needs to rest
until the end of the month.
This isn't a hotel.
He has been here for over a week,
and it's time he went home.
We're short on beds as it is.
I'll have you discharged within the week.
I made myself very clear.
[Sungwoo] Hey, leave it.
She's a total nutcase.
She's the hospital director's daughter,
and she never backs down.
Go talk to the director in person.
[sighs]
[sighs] I can't stand jerks
who pretend to be ill.
[exclaims] I wish he'd just disappear.
No more vertical wrinkles.
Smile, Yoon Jingyeong.
Relax your facial muscles.
[exhales]
[doctor] Hey, Yoon Jingyeong!
[panting]
Jingyeong, I need a favor.
-I'm on night watch today--
-Oh, my dear senior doctor.
I would pretend to die
if you told me to die.
But I can't swap with you today.
The most important appointment
of my life is today.
[inhales deeply] I'm really sorry.
Hey, Jingyeong. Yoon Jingyeong!
Sorry!
[♪ live jazz music playing]
Wooju.
Hey.
[gasps in awe]
Did you have a blind date today?
You're all dressed up.
[chuckles] I didn't have a blind date.
I just dressed for the location.
Why did you book such a nice place?
It's too much pressure.
My grandma booked the table.
She told me to treat you
to something nice.
You made a house call to check on her
while your father was away?
[exclaims quizzically]
-Your grandmother made the reservation?
-Yes.
[chuckles softly]
I like the atmosphere.
What do you want to eat?
[♪ jazz music continues]
When the idol trainee dumped you,
you wailed so hard
that you got snot and tears all over me.
It was an expensive shirt, too.
We only dated for less than a month.
I was young and immature.
You weren't young. You were 23.
-The ice hockey player after that--
-That guy...
I dumped him, okay?
Whatever.
You came all the way to the US to cry.
I spent so much time with you
that I ruined my finals.
How about we cover up
each other's embarrassing past?
I know all about your ex
and the ex before that.
They came to me to complain
whenever you made them angry.
-What did they say?
-Why ask when you know?
"Kim Wooju, that son of a b****."
"The selfish punk
who cares only about himself."
"He's total scum."
Anyway, you're no longer welcome
in the blind date market.
Your grandmother knows that, too.
That's why she won't tell you
to go on blind dates.
[sighs] That's not good at all.
What should I do now?
So, I gave it some thought.
Who could possibly save you, Wooju?
There's no need to look very far.
The person could be under your nose.
This could be a bit flustering for you,
but listen carefully.
Actually, I...
-[♪ music stops]
-[all applauding, cheering]
-Jingyeong.
-Yes?
Were you...
looking at the back of my head?
What?
[hesitates] Why do you ask?
Someone said
the back of my head looked pretty.
-Who? A woman?
-Yes.
Well... [chuckles softly]
She saw it a long time ago,
but she still remembered it.
[chuckles softly]
Is that why you're in a good mood?
Because someone praised your head shape?
-I'm not in a good mood.
-You are.
You're a bit more upbeat than usual.
Did you meet your first love or something?
You should become a psychic.
-You actually met her?
-Yes.
Actually,
I met the owner of the key ring.
What? She's alive?
-Here in Korea?
-Yes.
Where did you meet? Did she call?
Not really.
Do you remember Yoo Meri?
Yoo Meri?
The cactus girl?
-It's her?
-[chuckles] Yes.
[♪ poignant, melancholy music playing]
[exclaims in realization]
Do you see the goosebumps?
How did you figure it out?
Does she also know who you are?
No, she doesn't know yet.
Only I do.
[hums thoughtfully]
That's really fascinating.
It is.
[breathes deeply]
How did we meet again like this?
I've always wanted to ask.
Why didn't you look for her?
You could've tried to find her.
[acknowledges]
I did look for her.
[officer] Here's the address
the taxi driver put
on his witness statement.
I'm not sure if his family's still there.
He died in an accident
two weeks after the crash,
while coming in to give extra details.
[Youngsook] I just don't get it.
He talked to the police already.
Why would he go back there
to talk to them again?
He must've remembered something else.
Would that family appreciate it
when the couple's already dead?
Your dad ended up dead for being nosy.
If only he hadn't gone
to the police station.
[Youngsook sighs]
PREMIUM ORANGE JUICE GIFT SET
The truth is,
I was too scared to see her.
I was afraid she'd resent me.
So, I don't know what to do next.
Should I tell her or not?
Don't tell her.
[♪ melancholy music playing]
Well...
It would be best not to.
She might think
her father died because of you.
-Right?
-Yes.
You should consider her feelings, too.
Right.
[inhales deeply] I'm sorry, sir.
The interview was meant to explain
the social benefits of our raffle,
but they wrote something else
without consulting us.
It's fine.
It was your chance.
Since you are at it,
why didn't you say you planned
the Beauté Palace event,
and that you were behind
the 350% increase in sales?
The Young Entrepreneur Award
I got last year...
Why didn't you say you lobbied them
to give me your award, too?
-I apologize.
-Why are you always apologizing?
You work so hard, Sanghyeon.
I should give you a bonus.
Here.
It's fine. Come closer.
Come closer.
Hey, Sanghyeon.
You know what?
No matter how hard you try,
you can't be me.
[♪ tense melancholy music playing]
Was it in middle school?
We became friends
because you shielded me from the bullies.
My dad sent you abroad to study
and made you Managing Director
only because you were my friend.
I get the impression
that you're mistaken sometimes.
[chuckles]
But then our pet dog, a shih tzu,
thinks it's human
because it's fed and bathed.
Spend that on some kibble.
[inhales] I'll heed your warning.
[♪ foreboding music playing]
I should've just stayed to work late.
What a waste of an expensive meal.
[sighs wearily]
Don't tell her.
[♪ melancholy music playing]
Well, it would be best not to.
She might think
her father died because of you.
Right.
You're a coward, Jingyeong.
Why did I say that,
knowing he would get hurt?
[♪ playing "Chopsticks" on piano]
[♪ "Chopsticks" continues]
[♪ somber piano music playing]
[sighs softly]
[♪ piano music fades]
[wooden fish taps rhythmically]
MAIN HALL
[monk chanting prayers]
[chanting continues]
[wooden fish rhythmic taps continue]
[sighing in exhaustion]
Why does Mom have so much to say?
Oh, I'm starving.
What's for breakfast?
It's obvious.
The place across the road
we go to every year.
Oh, that gukbap again?
We can't have that every single year
just because Uncle used to like it.
Don't you think
it's time to assume he would be sick
of eating the same thing?
-[scoffs]
-It would be nice
to have pork cutlet sometimes.
We can't have that for breakfast!
I mean, Wooju likes it.
It's his birthday today.
What?
You're his only aunt,
and you don't know that?
He lived abroad most of the time.
People forget stuff after a while.
I feel really bad for the kid.
He never got to celebrate his birthday
since his parents died on that day.
He's lucky he wasn't kicked
out of the family.
Why do you think my brother died?
It was because Wooju--
-[Hangu] Honey.
-Yes, well, he was responsible for...
Couldn't you have made a sound at least?
Why is it so cold?
I'll go wait in the car.
Where are you...
Why do I feel so warm?
Wait for me.
[♪ melancholy music playing]
Wooju.
CONDOLENCES
Talk to your dad
if you have anything left to say.
You won't see him ever again.
Say what you want while you can.
[crying, breath trembling]
I'm sorry.
[sighs softly]
It was my fault.
[Kim Wooju's dad]
Are you still upset, Wooju?
It was my birthday present.
Why did you give it to Eungsoo?
It was mine.
He wanted it.
His whole family came
to wish you a happy birthday.
Couldn't you give him that?
I promise to buy you a new toy robot.
-Let it go.
-No.
Tell Eungsoo to give back what he took
and buy him the robot.
[whining] He always takes what's mine.
-He's a mean pig.
-[Kim Wooju's dad disapproving]
You can't talk like that
about your cousin.
Take it back.
Or Dad will get really angry.
You won't take it back?
You're a good boy, aren't you?
Do as your dad says.
Come on.
You won't take it back?
[Kim Wooju's dad sighs]
Then I won't buy you the toy robot.
[gasps] Honey!
[truck horn blaring]
-[all scream]
-[horn blaring]
[tires screeching]
[♪ tense melancholy music playing]
You mean...
Your dad was in the accident...
because he turned around to talk to you?
[man] What was that?
[breath trembling] Honey.
I lost my son because of you, Wooju?
[breathing heavily]
[sighs]
Okay.
Make sure Mom eats something, Ms. Kim.
Bye.
[line disconnects]
Grandma won't have breakfast?
She doesn't feel well.
She wouldn't feel like eating.
Today at least,
she'll think more of her dead son
than her dear grandson.
[Eungsoo] True.
Grandma didn't even glance at Wooju
during the whole service.
Even when Grandpa
chased him away to the US,
she only cared about Wooju, didn't she?
[scoffs]
We must have breakfast without them.
What should we eat?
How about malatang?
I found a famous place nearby.
Let's have tofu hot pot.
Why do you even ask? Don't ask me anymore.
I won't.
Are you okay with that?
What? Oh, yes. It's fine.
[♪ ominous music playing]
I TOOK CARE OF IT
[♪ ominous music crescendos]
[♪ ominous sting]
[rain pattering]
[thunder rumbling]
[exclaims quizzically]
It flowered.
[♪ whimsical music playing]
Don't sit on that one.
[Meri acknowledges]
Okay. [chuckles]
[thunder rumbling]
-[Grandad] What was that?
-[Grandma] Honey.
I lost my son because of you, Wooju?
He's lucky he wasn't kicked
out of the family.
Why do you think my brother died?
-It was because Wooju--
-[Hangu] Honey.
[♪ melancholy music playing]
[breathing heavily]
[continues breathing heavily]
[vibrating]
[panting]
CEO YOO MERI
[Meri] This cactus
must be a flowering kind.
[vibrating]
By the way, is it your birthday today?
[panting]
[rain pattering]
TEAM LEADER KIM WOOJU
BIRTHDAY: TODAY
I didn't know it was your birthday.
What kind of cake do you like?
I'll send you a cake coupon.
It's not a bribe.
-Allow me to congratulate you, at least.
-[panting]
[Kim Wooju] Will you buy me a meal, then?
I'm hungry.
[♪ soft orchestral music playing]
[Meri] How about a home-cooked meal?
[breathing slows]
[Meri gasps]
Does it sound like I'm flirting?
HOW ABOUT A HOME-COOKED MEAL?
If we were to meet someone from work
at a restaurant on a weekend,
-you might look--
-[Kim Wooju] I'm on my way.
[exhales]
Yes.
It's a Sunday.
Not many restaurants will be open.
He bought me naengmyeon last time.
He's always helping me out.
I can cook him a meal. Why not?
What do I have at home?
[♪ upbeat pop music playing]
Rice.
[Youngsook over phone] No, stop!
Add just enough water
to cover the seaweed.
You add water little by little
-to keep the broth nice and rich.
-Is that it?
-This much?
-Yes.
Now let that simmer,
and add the small octopus
at the last moment.
-Or it'll go tough.
-Okay.
Why are you suddenly cooking
seaweed soup with octopus?
I decided to cook for myself for once.
You, cook?
Why don't you grill a yellow croaker,
and heat up some yukjeon as well?
[chuckles]
I'm thawing them already.
[Youngsook gasps]
Did you invite someone?
[♪ feel-good music playing]
Like who? No one's coming.
I'm cooking for myself.
You're going to eat all that on your own?
Yes.
I need to free up some freezer space.
Of course, you do.
If you're making the effort,
why don't you bring out the pretty plates?
The ones you bought
to use after the wedding.
That's it. I'd forgotten about those.
Why go that far
when it's just me?
Let's hang up. I have a lot to do.
CALL ENDED
That brat.
She's too lazy
to even boil some scorched rice,
and she's cooking up a feast.
Who's coming that she won't tell me?
Is it a guy? [clicks tongue]
I'd be glad if it were.
[seagulls squawking]
Dear seagulls.
If it were someone like that team leader,
wouldn't I be pleased?
Seagulls.
[door closes, beeps]
-[Meri chuckles softly]
-[Kim Wooju gasps]
[♪ enthralling orchestral music laying]
[chuckles nervously]
It's your birthday,
and I wanted to thank you for everything.
-Take a seat.
-Thanks.
Did you prepare all this?
Well, yes, I guess?
This is what I usually eat.
I wanted to empty my fridge,
and I just had to get a few things
and heat them up.
It wasn't that much work.
It was pretty easy. [chuckles softly]
You must be hungry.
-Shall we eat?
-Yes.
-How is it?
-[clears throat]
When we have a guest over,
we serve seaweed soup with octopus.
It's a great energy boost.
[exclaims in realization, chuckles]
That's why it tastes like this.
It's rich, isn't it?
It is.
[♪ whimsical music playing]
[Kim Wooju clears throat]
It's salty.
It's so salty.
[phone vibrating]
[chuckles]
[Youngsook] Just in case you don't know,
don't add extra seasoning to the soup.
The octopus is salty enough.
[Meri] She took her time to tell me that.
[chuckles softly]
The soup is salty.
I should've tasted it
once more at the end.
That's fine. I'll water it down now.
[Kim Wooju chuckles]
[hums in satisfaction, gulps]
-It's perfect.
-[chuckles softly]
I'm sure you had more than enough at home.
Don't eat that. Have something else.
Some japchae.
-[Kim Wooju acknowledges]
-That should be fine.
The braised short ribs are great.
Have some meat, too.
[♪ whimsical sting]
Ms. Yoo, why do you treat me like this?
What?
Why would you cook all this for me?
Even my family
doesn't care about my birthday.
[hesitates]
I didn't know about that.
[exhales]
I haven't had seaweed soup in so long.
[sharp inhale] Was it when I was eight?
I think that was the last time.
I felt like
I shouldn't eat birthday soup.
My parents passed away on my birthday,
and it was my fault.
[♪ ominous sting]
So, instead of having seaweed soup,
I stuffed my face with rice.
Eating lots of rice made me sleepy,
so I could just sleep.
[♪ soft, gentle music playing]
When I woke up,
it would be the next day.
That's what I've done to forget that day.
That's why
it feels weird when I see people
who look forward to their birthday.
It feels awkward when someone
wishes me a happy birthday.
Thanks for celebrating with me, though.
[chuckles softly]
[hums in satisfaction, slurps]
Good for you.
For sleeping the whole day.
There are 365 days in a year.
It doesn't matter
if you erase one from your mind.
When things get too tough,
it's best to just run away.
[♪ upbeat pop music playing]
Let's eat a lot
and save up our energy.
Okay.
[Kim Wooju hums in satisfaction]
Oh, right.
-[chuckling]
-It's so terribly salty.
-Ms. Yoo.
-Yes?
Right here...
No.
Let me...
[♪ ethereal sparkle]
[clears throat]
When did that happen?
Hey.
It's a double rainbow.
Mr. Kim.
[♪ enchanting music playing]
Hurry.
[exclaims in awe]
No way.
Quick, make a wish.
-What?
Don't you know
the three best times to make a wish?
When the first snow falls,
as you hold your breath in a tunnel,
and to a double rainbow.
Those wishes come true.
[scoffing]
Says who? Who even believes that?
[♪ enchanting music continues]
-What did you wish for?
-What about you?
I wished that everything would work out.
That I'd make lots of money,
and that my mom wouldn't get sick.
I want my career to take off
and no one to find out about the house.
-Wow, you ask for a lot.
-What did you wish for?
[hums thoughtfully]
[clears throat]
Hey, come on.
You won't tell?
[♪ whimsical music playing]
I don't remember.
You don't remember?
Tell me. I want to know.
Oh, I don't remember.
You agreed to tell me.
-When did I say that?
-That didn't work.
That's not fair. I told you my wishes.
-Don't ask.
-Then spit out the food you just ate.
[imitates retching]
[Kim Wooju] In that short moment,
I made a wish.
That the wishes of the woman
who gave me a way out whenever I was
at a dead end would come true.
Okay, then.
Tell me if I catch you.
[♪ dramatic sting]
[Meri screams, gasps]
[slow, rhythmic heartbeats]
[♪ upbeat dreamy music playing]
WOULD YOU MARRY ME?
[Kim Wooju] Didn't you say
he was in Hong Kong?
[Meri] Do you think
he came here knowingly?
[Jingyeong] Thank you for that day.
[Meri] I want to be with someone
who's there for me when I'm struggling.
[Sejung] What's this? What do we do?
[Kim Wooju] We should go.
[Wooju] ...lives at Beauté Palace.
I went there for something
and saw someone who looked just like you.
[Meri] You must've been mistaken.
Where will you sleep, then?
That room...
-[Kim Wooju] I'll sleep here.
-[Meri] What?
[Jingyeong] Back out of it right now.
What if your grandmother finds out?
This makes you an accomplice.
[Wooju] Did you have fun
living your fake newlywed life?
Translated by Jennifer Jean Lim